It is September 21st, and today
we are going to celebrate Christmas.
It's not that heavy.
This is Christmas' box.
It may look like a small box,
to have every Christmas ornament,
and that is because...
it is, it is very small.
I mean-
look at the size of the tree, like-
it's smaller than my arm.
But anyway, it's nothing,
the spirit is what counts,
the spirit and what's here, in our heart.
The Christmas decorations are so sparse that in theory
this would only be enough to decorate my room and that's it,
because it's not enough for this whole house.
I am going to start the house from the foundation
and I am going to place the legs on the tree,
because if we start from the roof, bad stuff.
Ok.
I'm going to start with the bows,
little bulbs, bulbs, christmas bulbs,
uh, I can see my reflection on this one.
Oh... how horrible.
Oops nononononononononononononono-
this has to be symetric.
Ah sh**
this goes at the beginning.
I think this is called serpentina
[apparently not]
because it's like a snake.
Maybe you are wondering,
Why is she decorating a Christmas tree-
when she already has one that's decorated in the background?
Because if not it's  not Christmas.
The fun part about Christmas is
having to spend time with your family,
See? With your family-
Where is my family?
In family, here is my mammoth.
My sister says it's hers, but I say it's mine.
I'm going to try to place the ornaments with just one hand.
With my left hand, which is my non dominant hand.
That way it will get some practice and ability
ah, I would love to be ambidextrous,
but... fu**
Please! No! It's becoming worse.
Please, oh, nice!
Oh, this is too dificult.
It looks like I am not going to be ambidextrous ever in my lifetime.
Ah, that's it, I give up.
What is this? What is this ridiculousness?
Oh my god, it's turning out bad.
Ok, and... that would be it.
Now that we have our tree, it's turn to do
the nativity scene
The nativity scene is something that it's usually put up
in all houses in Spain,
but this time I didn't want-
I didn't want to do the traditional scene.
So what I am going to do
is take a picture of New York
and interpret it as the nativity scene.
This will be our Rockefeller Center tree,
and up next, this paper will be the ice skating rink,
it will be the ice.
And now in this picture there is something like a stand here,
and I am going to use this hut.
We also have the walls-
You place it like this, and that's it-
And now we have the characters:
the skaters in this case.
we have the main family,
the Three Kings,
the animals,
and the shepherds.
The characters.
It's so similar,
that I would understand if you couldn't differentiate between
my navity scene, from New York's picture.
Next on the list are Christmas carols.
I brought an assistant, so that-
she can help me with the carols.
Where do we start?
Wherever you want-
Our assistant just decided to abandon us.
Let's start with the first song.
[I'm not going to translate this lol-]
-the fish in the river when they see God be born.
That's what I said.
Yeah? Are you sure?
Yeah
If you are an assistant but then you leave, you cannot correct me.
I would like to say
that I am an carol singing expert,
but it would be a lie.
cottage cheese, butter and wine-.
But apparently I'm not very good,
But what I am an expert at, is in being annoying.
Then, is that why you are cebrating Christmas now?
To be a pain in the a**?
Uh? Uh? Who said that?
I think I heard someone say something.
Yes, I did!
I said if that is the reason
why you are celebrating Christmas now,
to be a pain in the a**.
In effect, that is why.
Next in the list,
is an advent.
Advent is a Christmas calendar,
and since it's not Christmas now, and they are not selling the advent,
I will have to make and create my own advent.
An advent is a chocolate calendar,
that goes from December the 1st,
to December the 24th.
And each day, you eat a chocolate.
To be honest, the advent's chocolate is delicious.
It's one of the most delicious chocolates I have ever tried in my life.
And yes,
at my age I still eat advents, Ok?
The truth is that Christmas is a season
very good to do crafts,
like this one.
That well, more than an advent,
this is a mess, but anyway.
Perfect, we have our advent.
Can you see? The professionalism.
No.
Another of the important events to prepare in Christmas,
Are the presents.
And the theme for summer is:
useless presents.
therefore, I am going to gift my father a piece of play dough.
My sister is going to get this paper,
And my mother is going to get
this piece from the Christmas tree,
so that she can always take Christmas with her.
She is gonna love it.
Since it's Christmas, uh, I've got you a present.
Do I have to open it?
Yes-
How beautiful.
Do you like it?
I am very excited.
I must say that the theme is: useless things
Translate it for me later.
Nice, nice...
Nice present?
Nice, yes, nice present, useless thing.
We said that in Christmas come
Santa Claus and the Three Kings, right?
Well, since they come, we have to give them some food,
since they have a long trip.
And now we have to wait for Santa Claus to come.
I came to bring presents, I am Santa Claus.
They could have at least left a coffee, as the night is long.
I don't want cookies.
Oh! What is this?
Oh! Sugar.
My spoon has something green stuck on it.
And I licked it.
Anyway.
No way,
I wasn't expecting that.
Santa Claus came.
I am surprised Santa Claus didn't complain
about the milk's taste.
I don't know how long this has gone without being washed...
And well, it's already
Christmas
Christmas in September,
Which by the way, for years
I have been mixing up September and December.
They are so similar.
SeptemberDecemberSeptemberDecember-
It's like a tongue tier.